[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Many microphones use this shape because of its specific properties.", "correct_answer": "Parabola", "incorrect_answers": ["Ellipse", "Circle", "Hyperbola"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which dress sizes are for those who are 5 1 tall, with an average bust but a shorter back?", "correct_answer": "Junior Petite", "incorrect_answers": ["Miss Petite", "Junior", "Young Junior"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do the terrorists want in the action film Die Hard?", "correct_answer": "Bearer bonds", "incorrect_answers": ["Release of foreign prisoners", "To kill as many people as possible", "To kidnap the companys owner"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sharks must eat continually in order to survive.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The tail bone is scientifically known as the coccyx.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie Dont Tell Mom the Babysitters Dead was released on June 7, 1991.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These are compounds that help protect cells from free radicals.", "correct_answer": "antioxidants", "incorrect_answers": ["calories", "phytochemicals", "nutrients"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Most estate agents find it difficult to sell a house, numbered thirteen.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is a female sheep called or known as?", "correct_answer": "ewe", "incorrect_answers": ["colt", "fleece", "ram"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Zorro from the 1940 movie The Mark of Zorro was listed as one of the best movie heroes in history by the American Film Institute. What does Zorros name mean in Spanish?", "correct_answer": "Fox", "incorrect_answers": ["Panther", "Wind", "Flash"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the tagline from the theatrical release poster of the 1994 movie Speed?", "correct_answer": "Get ready for rush hour.", "incorrect_answers": ["Sometimes speed saves lives.", "As fast as you can.", "Things are gonna get racy."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the main ingredient of the traditional Spanish dish paella?", "correct_answer": "Rice", "incorrect_answers": ["Lentils", "Dough", "Potatoes"]}]